<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HEALxLM 25</title>
    <link>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/</link>
    <description>Recent content on HEALxLM 25</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Accepted Papers</title>
      <link>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/accepted/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/accepted/</guid>
      <description>Accepted Papers We received a total of 15 submissions to the workshop, out of which we selected 9 for presentation to the workshop. We thank all authors and reviewers for their contribution to the DIGITA Workshop. Authors Title </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dates</title>
      <link>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/dates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/dates/</guid>
      <description>TBD</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organization</title>
      <link>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/organization/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/organization/</guid>
      <description>Committees Organizing Committee Gianluca Aguzzi, Department of Computer Science and Engineering - Alma Mater Studiorum University of Bologna, Italy Sara Montagna, Department of Pure and Applied Science - University of Urbino Carlo Bo, Italy Mauro Dragoni, Fondazione Bruno Kessler (FBK), Italy Program Committee TBD</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Previous Events</title>
      <link>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/previous/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/previous/</guid>
      <description>Previous Events Despite changing the name, this workshop represents the second edition of the MADTECC (Medical Applications with Digital Twins and Edge-Cloud Continuum) workshop, following its debut at PerCom 2024. This year, we aim to broaden the scope of the topics, keeping the spirit of involving researchers working in practical applications of Digital Twins to complex ecosystems without the constraints on the specific domain of healthcare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program</title>
      <link>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/program/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/program/</guid>
      <description>Program TBD
Keynote </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call for papers</title>
      <link>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/cfp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/cfp/</guid>
      <description>Call for Papers Recent advancements in generative AI have paved the way for powerful Language Model techniques to be applied in health-related contexts, offering potential benefits for healthcare providers and patients. These models can support medical professionals by aiding diagnosis, treatment planning, and process optimisation, offering patients more accessible and immediate guidance. However, several challenges must be addressed to ensure safe and effective use. Key issues include the accuracy and reliability of medical information, as any misinformation could have serious consequences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/about/</guid>
      <description>The 23nd International Conference on Pervasive Computing and Communications (PerCom 2025) March 17 – 21, 2025, Washington DC, USA (Walter E. Washington Convention Center) Conference Overview IEEE PerCom, now in its 23rd year, will be held at Walter E. Washington Convention Center in Washington DC, USA, from March 17 – 21, 2025, as a physical in-person conference. PerCom is the premier annual scholarly venue in pervasive computing and communications. Pervasive computing is constantly at the forefront of mobile systems research and has found its way into many commercial systems due to tremendous advances in a broad spectrum of technologies and topics such as wireless networking, mobile and distributed computing, sensor systems, ambient intelligence, and smart devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/search/placeholder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/search/placeholder/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Posts Archive</title>
      <link>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/archive/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
