<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on HEALxLM 25</title>
    <link>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on HEALxLM 25</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Accepted Papers</title>
      <link>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/accepted/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/accepted/</guid>
      <description>Accepted Papers Authors Title </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dates</title>
      <link>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/dates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/dates/</guid>
      <description>Dates Paper submission deadline: April 24th, 2025
Paper notification: May 15th, 2025
Camera ready deadline: June 6th, 2025
Workshop: June 26th, 2025</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organization</title>
      <link>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/organization/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/organization/</guid>
      <description>Committees Organizing Committee Gianluca Aguzzi, Department of Computer Science and Engineering - Alma Mater Studiorum University of Bologna, Italy Sara Montagna, Department of Pure and Applied Science - University of Urbino Carlo Bo, Italy Mauro Dragoni, Fondazione Bruno Kessler (FBK), Italy Program Committee Alaa Alashi, Yale University, USA Patrizio Bellan, Fondazione Bruno Kessler, Italy Marco Bombieri, University of Verona, Italy Elena Cabrio, University of Côte d&amp;rsquo;Azur, France David Chartash, Yale University, USA Philipp Cimiano, University of Bielefeld, Germany Thomas Huang, Yale University, USA Adam Jatowt, University of Innsbruck, Austria Markus Kreuzthaler, Medical University of Graz, Austria Amila Kugic, Medical University of Graz, Austria Simone Magnolini, Fondazione Bruno Kessler, Italy Francesco Osborne, Open University, UK Simone Paolo Ponzetto, University of Mannheim, Germany Marco Rospocher, University of Verona, Italy Conrad Safranek, Yale University, USA Leonardo Sanna, Fondazione Bruno Kessler, Italy Stefan Schulz, Medical University of Graz, Austria Vimig Socrates, Yale University, USA R.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Previous Events</title>
      <link>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/previous/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/previous/</guid>
      <description>Previous Events Despite changing the name, this workshop represents the second edition of the MADTECC (Medical Applications with Digital Twins and Edge-Cloud Continuum) workshop, following its debut at PerCom 2024. This year, we aim to broaden the scope of the topics, keeping the spirit of involving researchers working in practical applications of Digital Twins to complex ecosystems without the constraints on the specific domain of healthcare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program</title>
      <link>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/program/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/program/</guid>
      <description>Program TBD
Keynote </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call for papers</title>
      <link>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/cfp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heal-xlm-workshop.github.io/2025/cfp/</guid>
      <description>Call for Papers Recent advancements in generative AI have paved the way for powerful Language Model techniques to be applied in health-related contexts, offering potential benefits for healthcare providers and patients. These models can support medical professionals by aiding diagnosis, treatment planning, and process optimisation, offering patients more accessible and immediate guidance. However, several challenges must be addressed to ensure safe and effective use. Key issues include the accuracy and reliability of medical information, as any misinformation could have serious consequences.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
